https://www.preview.com.au/privacy-policy

1300 799 209CONTACT
0
Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyAt Preview Plastics we respect the privacy of every individual who visits our website.This privacy statement provides notice of the standards and terms under which we protect the privacy of information supplied by visitors to our website.This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically to review this information.Preview Plastics receives data about its website visitors only when such information is provided voluntarily, such as when a visitor requests information or a quote, makes a purchase or sends us an e-mail.When you provide personally identifiable information to us through our website, it will be used only to fulfil your specific request. We do reserve the right, at our discretion, to send you information about specials or services. We will not, however, sell or trade your personally identifiable information unless we are authorized or legally required to do so.Preview Plastics takes all reasonable steps to ensure your information remains secure, and to prevent unauthorised access to your information. We use our best efforts to ensure that information received via this website remains secure within our systems, however users should be aware that there are inherent risks in transmitting information across the Internet. We are not responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.The Preview Plastics website does not use cookies to automatically gather information about you when you visit our website.  We are an Australian owned and operated Company offering great Customer Service.Specializing in PVC and Polypropylene Products, Menu Covers, Matting and Archival storage.  Login Username or email address *
Password *
Login
Remember me
Lost your password? Search for:
Search for:
Pockets & SleevesPlastic PocketsId HoldersPlastic ProductsLibrary & EducationTrade Plate HoldersPrinted WalletsBA Control BoardsCustom MadeDisplay StandsPromotional ProductsCustom RulersPlastic PrintingPlastic Pockets & SleevesCustom Plastic ProductsRing BindersAudit BagsAudit BagsOther ProductsArchival StorageMatsMenu CoversSignsNo products in the cart.
